Sit down.
Have a few drinks with me.
After drinking, we'll be friends.
I, Tang Huiyao, naturally won't make things difficult for a friend.
Get the hell away from me.
This lady needs a friend like you?
I'm giving you face.
A woman I've taken a liking to...
Let go of me!
...never gets away.
Clear the room.
Get out! Go!
Let go!
Let go of me!
You dare to harass this lady?
Take one more step...
...and I'll crack your skull open.
A great beauty...
...talking about fighting is so boring.
What are you doing?
I need to report...
...the daily accounts to Second Master Tang.
Move aside.
Second Master Tang isn't here.
Report tomorrow.
Bullshit.
Second Master Tang said...
...he must know the daily accounts.
At least let me...
...put this file on his desk.
Not letting me in, huh?
Fine.
When Second Master Tang asks about it...
...I'll say you two stopped me.
Okay?
Well...
Go on, get moving.
Young Master Tang is throwing a fit inside.
Hurry up and go.
Go, go, go! Hurry!
Get out of my way!
Move!
Er Ni.
Zhao Fengsheng is just a dog begging for scraps.
Follow me...
...and you can have anything in Bian Shui.
Hold her down for me.
Let me go!
Even the wildest horse...
...I will ride.
Let go!
Let me go!
Hold her down.
Let go!
Coward.
If you have the guts, let me go!
Tang Huiyao, you're looking for death!
Playing the hero to save the beauty?
Zhao Fengsheng.
Get this straight.
She, in front of everyone...
...accused my Tang Family casino of cheating.
You, as the casino manager...
...tell me how we resolve this.
Shengzi.
They set me up.
I'm asking you.
How do we resolve it?
Er Ni came with me.
What does Young Master Tang want to do?
I, Zhao Fengsheng, will take it.
You'll take responsibility?
Good.
I'll give you this chance.
This first bottle...
...is for her saying my Tang Family casino cheats.
The second bottle...
...is compensation for her slapping me.
This third one...
...is for your negligence as casino manager.
So you're saying...
...if I finish these three bottles today...
...today's matter is settled?
Considering my father...
...personally recruited you...
...I'll give you this face.
Shengzi.
This is all strong liquor.
Three bottles will kill you.
Don't worry.
You know how much I can drink.
The Tang Family's liquor is good stuff.
Might as well drink it.
Manager Zhao.
If you can't drink this...
...my boys here can help pour it down your throat.
No need for your concern, Young Master Tang.
This is my spiritual fuel.
It only gives me more energy.
Shengzi.
This guy can really drink.
Young Master Tang.
This is 42-proof baijiu.
The kick will hit him soon.
Shengzi.
I'll drink it for you.
Little sister Er Ni.
You're drunk.
Aren't you afraid I'll lay hands on you?
I'm fine.
Keep drinking.
Shengzi.
Let's see how long you can keep up the act.
Drink it!
Shengzi.
This liquor is really good.
Get the hell out of my way
What?
Let go of me!
Get up.
You wanna drink, huh?
Let me go!
Drink!
You like to pretend, don't you?
Screwing things up for me, huh?
Let go!
Drink.
Keep pretending!
Drink it!
Drink.
Drink!
Huiyao.
Stop!
Dad.
You...
What are you doing here?
Shengzi.
Brother Shengzi.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
Second Master Tang.
I failed to manage the place properly.
It's my fault.
I'll drink.
I know what happened.
Brother Shengzi has already drunk two bottles.
Let's end this matter here.
Dad...
Shut up.
Thank you, Second Master.
I was wrong.
From now on...
It won't happen again.
Old Mu! Old Mu!
Old Mu, hurry!
Zhao Fengsheng.
Don't vomit on Second Master.
Let go.
A perfectly good place...
Look what you've turned it into.
Let go.
Get him out of here, now!
Dad...
Are my words meaningless?
Shengzi.
Let's go.
Dad.
A hoodlum like Zhao Fengsheng...
Is worth you protecting him like this?
I'm protecting him?
Zhao Fengsheng has deep ties to Li Xiangping.
He can't die in our casino.
And the Old Street matter isn't settled yet.
Now is not the time to go to war with the Li Family.
You're so interested in a shabby old street?
We have plenty of other business we can do.
This Old Street...
is the most profitable business.
Old Street can make money?
Look.
What is this?
A gold bracelet of such fine quality.
Where did you get it?
Stole it from Zhao Fengsheng's house.
Zhao...
Zhao Fengsheng's house?
Where would a hoodlum like him get that kind of money?
Zhao Fengsheng...
doesn't know this bracelet is with me.
He also doesn't know...
that beneath Old Street lies a top-tier gold mine.
A top-tier gold mine?
How big is it?
Bracelets like this, produced by the ton.
By the ton.
That's a business worth billions.
Dad...
Are you telling the truth?
Once I extract the gold...
we can arm ourselves.
Then, forget about Bian Shui...
even that Li Xiangping...
won't be a match for us father and son.
Good.
It's okay.
Just get it all out.
Check if anyone's following us.
No one.
That's good.
I've already located Tang Hongtu's office.
Too many people during the day, hard to act.
I'll go again tonight.
You're going back?
Tang Huiyao won't let you off.
It's called hiding in plain sight.
They all think I'm drunk as a dog.
So this is the perfect time.
Let me go with you.
I almost got you killed just now.
I don't want the things I regret...
to increase by one more.
Listen to me.
Two people are too big a target.
Shengzi.
Listen to me.
Then you must be careful.
Don't worry.
I'll come back.